http://www.judaicailluminations.com/pages/terms-policies

Specialty Pages from The Illuminated Torah
More...
Terms & Policies
Privacy PolicyAt Judaica Illuminations, we want you to have the best shopping experience possible. While it is necessary for us to collect certain personal information, we respect and protect your right to privacy. The following policy is designed to answer any questions and concerns you may have regarding your privacy and the security of your information. If you have any additional questions or concerns, please contact us at customerservice@judaicailluminations.com.What Information Do We Collect and How?
Ordering InformationJudaica Illuminations keeps track of information in order to give you a more enjoyable, convenient shopping experience. Before completing your first purchase, we will ask you for your name, phone number, email, billing and shipping addresses. This information, along with your credit card number, is necessary to fulfill your order.All information not necessary to fulfill your order is optional. Note: It is not necessary to provide us with information to view our site.
CookiesIn revolutionizing the way you shop, Judaica Illuminations uses new technologies to better serve our customer. This includes using "cookies" so you can best experience our site. Cookies are bits of electronic information placed over the internet onto your computer. We do not store personal information about you or your finances using cookies. Cookies are standard on the internet and utilized by most websites whether you are aware of it or not. However, if you wish, most browsers can be set to prevent cookies or to notify you when one is being placed. Although cookies are not necessary to view our site, Judaica Illuminations recommends their use for the best experience possible.
How We Protect Your InformationJudaica Illuminations is committed to protecting the information we receive from you. Our site encrypts your credit card number and other personal information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology to provide for the secure transmission of the information from your PC to our servers. In addition, only those employees who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed such access. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies may be subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.
Secure Shopping at Judaica IlluminationsAt Judaica Illuminations, you can shop with confidence. We use SSL and Verisign encryption technology, digital certificates, secure commerce servers, and authentication to ensure that your personal information is secure online.
Typos and OmissionsWhile Judaica Illuminations tries very hard to ensure the accuracy of the information we provide, we are not responsible for vendor availability, typographical errors, technical inaccuracies, product pricing errors or omissions. Judaica Illuminations has the right to cancel any orders placed for any product listed at an incorrect price or shown with incorrect information, whether due to typographical error or otherwise and whether or not your order was accepted or your credit card charged. Upon any such cancellation, if your credit card has already been charged for the purchase, Judaica Illuminations will promptly issue a full credit to your account.
Changes in PolicyYou acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of the terms of service and you agree that using this site signifies your assent to Judaica Illuminations' Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use our site. Judaica Illuminations reserves the right to change the terms of service, including this Privacy Policy, at any time. We will post any changes so that you are always aware of our policy.
